peoplematters.in 2016-01-22

# Privacy and Policy — People Matters

  * About
  * Careers
  * Submission Guidelines
  * Advertise
  * Become a Sponsor
  * Contact Us
  * Feedback
  * Privacy Policy
  * Terms of Use
  * FAQs

## People Matters Online Privacy Policy

At People Matters, we care about online security as much as you do, so we’ve taken steps to ensure your personal information is safe and that all your https://www.peoplematters.in transactions are secure.

### How We Collect Personal Information

Our Web site uses various forms and methods to make it convenient for you get the best from the website services. This requires that you give us contact information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number or credit card information (in the case of the payment gateway facility).

We collect aggregate information on what pages you access or visit and information volunteered by you, such as site registrations. This information is used for:

  * Internal review
  * Improving the content of our Web pages
  * Contacting you with information about our organization, products and services.

The information collected is discarded and never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

### How We Keep Information Secure

People Matters uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving member and non-member data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place at our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

### Links to Other Sites

The People Matters Web site may contain links to other Web sites that are not owned or controlled by People Matters. People Matters is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other Web sites. You are advised to read the privacy statements of any linked site. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

### Using Our Bulletin Boards and Online Surveys

When using People Matters Bulletin Boards, users are asked to abide by basic rules of etiquette.

Online survey data will be reported in aggregate. No individual company data is ever released or identified. Unique survey identifiers (e.g., member identification number) are kept confidential and will only be used by authorized People Matters staff to get in contact with survey participants if necessary.

### How to Contact Us

You can contact us at [info@peoplematters.in](mailto:info@peoplematters.in) People Matters reserves the right to change its privacy policy. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page and will be effective immediately upon posting. By using our Web site, you signify that you agree to the People Matters Online Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site.

If you have questions about this privacy statement or the practices of this Web site, please contact us at [info@peoplematters.in](mailto:info@peoplematters.in)
